Here's some more.
Just work things out.
Hey, mano, come on.
Get another beer.
Alright!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Come on, people! Move it!
Time is money!
Let's-- Move! Move! Move faster!
What, did we tell you
to slow down?
Come on! Hustle! Hustle!
Hustle, goddammit!
Move!
Did I tell you to slow down?
Goddammit, move!
All units, stand by.
Retain any evidence
before they can destroy it.
Repeat, retain any evidence.
Go, go, go!
DEA! Get on the floor now!
-Shit!
-Get on the damn floor!
Move! Move!
Oh, shit! It's the Feds!
DEA!
DEA! Get your hands up!
Hands up!
- Drop the meth!
- Put your hands up!
Don't even think about it
or we will shoot!
Get the fuck down! Don't move!
Someone tell me
what these have in common.
Apex predators?
Correct.
Apex predators are at the top
of the food chain.
Unchallenged
in their ecosystem...
by any other natural predator.
Kyle!
Yeah?
Why are apex predators
exceptionally aggressive?
Because they have to be?
Perhaps more eloquently?
Um...
It is their evolutionary
instinct to have unmatched--
Ferocity.
They hunt. They live.
That's all.
Aggression is simply
a means of survival.
Kyle!
Oh, my God!
Hi, Alice!
Oh, my God,
I missed you so much!
-Yeah, I've missed you too.
-How are you?
I'm OK.
You look amazing.
Oh, my God, they're here.
-We should go.
-Huh?
So, this is where
you've been hiding.
Kyle, the biology student.
I'm so sorry.
I had to.
She was Jamie's friend too.
And when she found out
we were scattering his ashes
in the Keys, well...
Plus, we needed a ride, so...
I'm really sorry.
I sold my car and--
-What?
-I-I needed the money,
but I'll tell you
everything later.
Yo, Kyle! Alice!
Let's make tracks!
Please be nice.
Be patient. Please?
Yeah?
You've got him?
Yeah.
So, what happened to your car?
You loved that thing.
It was about time.
I was barely using it,
so I sold it.
Dude, that thing
was like a left nut to you.
Come on.
It was my mom.
She's at it again.
Got ahold
of my chequeings account.
Shit. How bad?
She cleared me out at the races.
Twelve thousand dollars.
Plus, her 27
to loan sharks, so...
-Oh, my God.
-And I dropped out.
What?
I need money, Kyle.
I'm working pretty much
every hour God sends.
You guys sing. This is my jam.
I said no smoking.
I forgot.
Whoa!
And it's ten points for Sam,
the man!
-That was ten out of ten.
-I'd give it a ten out of ten.
Thank you. Thank you. Ha-ha!
I'm gonna grab a burger
and some beer.
-You guys want?
-Yeah. I'll take another beer.
- Obviously.
- Yeah? Kyle?
Yeah. Sure, I'll take one.
OK!
Alright!
She's not all bad.
God, she grates me.
Yeah, but I mean,
who doesn't, right?
You.
And Jamie, of course.
Kyle...
I'm only saying this
because I love you, but...
Not right now,
but at some point,
you know you have to start
moving on.
You know...
I never understood
why people say that.
I mean, how is anyone
supposed to move on
from losing someone
that they love?
I loved him too.
Yeah, well, it would be great
if for a second,
people would just stop
telling me how to be.
Kyle.
-What's up her ass?
-You, for one.
What'd I do?
-You want me to go talk to her?
-No.
What up, little sis?
Yo, where the hell are you?
Stop stalling and get your ass
on this thing.
Not happening.
I get it.
OK? Promise, I do.
But hiding away,
thinking about preserving life,
just means you're not living it.
Mm-hmm. Hum a little.
There we go.
Wakey, wakey!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Get up, get up, get up!
Let's make tracks today, people!
Get up!
Kyle, I see you.
OK, let's hit it.
Coming.
- Ooh!
- You have two minutes.
Got it. Alrighty.
Hey, can somebody get me
a soda while I'm in there?
Make it quick!
Y'all see this?
It's gator country.
Y'all better stay out
of the water.
I ain't coming
to save none of y'all.
I'm gonna save my own ass.
Whoa, Sam, reapers.
Gator attacks.
Out for blood.
Stay out of the water.
That'll save you.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. That's her, alright.
That's who?
The big one.
Scar deep as a valley.
Yo, Kyle.
Let's go.
- Y'all take care now, you hear?
- Come on, let's go.
I don't know
if I can recover from you.
Well, can you
drive safer this time?
-We still got some miles to go.
-What do you mean?
Why do I get the feeling
you're not telling me something?
Guys, I'm sorry
about last night.
It's just hard, you know?
You don't need
to apologise to us, Kyle.
We got you.
Gator parks, gators in the news.
This place
is gator-fucking-crazy.
It's big business.
Hey, you know how
much gator eggs go for?
A fucking fortune.
And this is my surprise
for you guys.
Why are we at an airport?
What the actual fuck?
What?
OK, ungrateful much?
I figured we'd get there quicker
and spend more time at the Keys,
not just driving there.
Yeah, what a great idea.
You do realise Kyle's terrified
of flying, right?
Yeah. But what?
We've all just got to stay
on the ground
for the rest of our lives?
Tell her to swallow
some bad bitch and let's go.
Oh, shit.
Fucking...
Fucking kids.
Welcome to Frank Airlines.
Well, she ain't pretty,
but she works.
Kind of.
Let's get you people on board.
You're late, and it's hotter
than a post-chili shit out here.
-Hey, is this for real?
-Ew.
-Hey, uh, Frank...
-Jesus Christ.
I mean, I'm pretty sure
that smoking on an airfield
is a big no-no, right?
Hey, bud.
You probably want to get
pro-smoking pretty quick.
Or you might find those Bijou
sneaks ain't gonna look so good
when you've trekked
a thousand miles to Florida.
Are you feeling me, compadre?
Good.
Fucking pussy.
I don't mind driving.
- Yeah. Play music.
- Yeah.
No.
We're doing this together,
right?
Come on.
OK.
Alright.
Fuck.
I would not want
to be stranded with those lot
on a deserted island.
Two tours, you know
what I learned?
Don't underestimate people.
OK. Listen, people.
Today's destination is Florida.
Now, we're gonna be landing
on a buddy of mine's airfield
west of Gainesville.
Now, people come to me,
means you want the scenic route.
So we'll fly out toward
the ocean and pitch a left.
Now, we're gonna be flying
real low and hugging the coast
so you can see the wetlands
in all its glory.
Sound good?
Sounds good to me.
OK, please, entrez.
Get on, people. Let's hustle.
Time is money.
Yes, yes.
Come on.
You pack those things
for the both of us?
Malika, where did you
find this guy?
Does it matter?
He's drunk and he's smoking.
Man the hell up.
Oh, hi, Damian.
Yeah, what's the latest?
Sorry, I've been offline.
Excuse me, sir, but you need
to switch your phone off.
Uh, yeah, 15 million.
No, I want 25.
Fifteen's embarrassing.
Hey, man,
you really need
to put that phone down.
I'll get that to you.
Just, give me an hour.
I'll have landed by then.
Put the goddamn phone down
before I shove it up your ass.
Take a day off, Roseanne.
Sorry, Damian. Ahem.
That's it.
Come on--
Clarence!
Hell of a job.
Everyone OK back there?
Honey, hold on!
We got a problem
with engine one.
- Shut it off.
- Right.
-What's going on?
-I'm wigging out, alright?
Baby! Aah!
Kyle?
You good?
-We're gonna get out of here.
-OK, what's the problem?
Just hold on, Alice.
We might be in trouble.
Engine two is on fire!
-Extinguishers!
This plane's going down.
We'll have to ditch it.
Ray!
OK, we lost engines.
We'll have to ditch it
somewhere, OK? You got that?
Oh, my God!
Whoa.
We'll have to call it in.
Call in the Mayday.
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
The radio isn't working!
Brace, brace, brace!
Oh, God! Get on your seat now!
Jamie?
Kyle? You alright?
Kyle?
Alright?
Kyle? It's OK.
Come on. Kyle?
You good?
Alright.
-Kyle?
-Come here.
Right, right, right.
How do I get there?
Alright, they're good.
- OK, OK...
- This way.
Come on, this way!
Wait.
-You good?
-Yeah, I'm OK.
There's no artery damage here.
This is clean. OK, OK, Zoe.
OK, we're good now. We're good.
Hey, hey, is it Zoe? Zoe?
Oh, fuck.
We can still fly, right?
-Stay here, OK?
-Who else is...
gone?
I'm sorry.
Just...
Alice, can you please
just wrap something around her?
Keep her warm, OK?
Just take care of her.
Give me two seconds, OK?
It's OK, huh?
-Yeah.
-OK.
Kyle. Kyle--
What?
Kyle, everybody's here
but that lady's husband.
Yeah, I know.
We survived.
-Hey, what is your name again?
-It's Frank.
Frank, do you have
a radio or a phone?
Radio's gone.
Phones won't work out here.
What I need is a tourniquet.
I need a belt.
-Get me a belt.
-OK, OK, OK!
-Your belt!
-What the fuck?
Don't flatter yourself.
Just give me the fucking belt.
Just hook that up.
Come on.
OK, I'm gonna wrap this
around you.
I'm gonna count to three,
and then I'm gonna pull, OK?
You just gotta breathe,
alright?
Three, two, one.
It's alright. We're gonna be OK.
We're gonna be OK.
Ray!
We need to find
a phone that works.
- There's no signal, Sam.
- You never know.
Ray!
Screw-top for Jamie's urn
was a really good idea.
- Yeah.
- Ray, goddammit!
Frank, who's he--
Who's he yelling at?
Ray!
The co-pilot.
There's no point
in searching solo.
When the rescue team comes,
they'll put a search out
or something, I don't...
No one's coming.
What do you mean
there's no one coming?
Frank, what do you fucking mean
- It was cheaper.
- What?
To fly unchartered.
-Am I right?
-Are you serious?
If the black box wasn't on,
no one knows that we're here.
This is the largest wetland
system in the entire US.
Even if they were
to figure it out,
what are the chances
that they're gonna find us?
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
Without shelter
from the heat and no food,
we can't wait here for them.
She's right.
We have to walk.
Walk?
Which way?
North. Maybe north-east.
Oh, OK.
Just kind of north
or north-east.
Is that it?
Now I feel better
that we have a solid plan.
We experienced problems
soon after we took off.
We pitched back north to try and
make it to an airfield, but--
We're so screwed.
We could be 20, 30,
maybe 40 miles away.
Experienced problems?
This isn't experiencing
problems.
Experiencing problems
is what happens
when you fly drunk, Frank.
Why don't you shut the fuck up?
Didn't your husband die,
like, five minutes ago?
Shouldn't you
be grieving quietly?
- Malika!
- Shut your mouth!
Hey! Stop it!
Guys, all we gotta do
is walk, OK?
Come on, just...
Let's just gather
whatever we can find, OK?
Phones, layers of clothing,
food.
And let's just get out of here.
Come on, guys.
Let's get to it.
OK, guys. What we got?
We got five phones.
Four are dead.
One is showing we are shit
out of luck for signal.
We got some scraps of food.
What else we got?
Guys.
Look!
Ray.
Ray!
Kyle!
Shit! Shit!
-Frank!
-Swim!
Shit!
Frank!
- Come on!
- Get out of the water!
-Get away from there!
-Oh, my God!
Come on, Frank!
Let's go!
Shit! Shit!
Where'd it go?
They just do not
go through humans like that.
There must be
a fucking nest around
because they're super
territorial.
Injured or not,
we gotta get out of here.
Frank, you said north.
Which way?
North... North...
Yeah. That way.
OK.
Fuck. Shit.
I need a time-out.
A recharge.
Can't go any further.
My heart, y'all.
Bet she wasn't
thinking about that
when she was washing down
XXL fries
with a gallon of cola
in front of a TV.
Jesus, Malika,
cut her some slack.
We're all dead, alright?
Actually, this looks
pretty good.
Haven't seen any gator tracks.
Solid ground away from water.
What now? What's wrong?
I'm just trying to figure out
who made her leader
because a few hours ago,
she wouldn't even
get on a plane,
and now she's like Steve Irwin
or some shit.
Well, she's the most qualified.
-I agree.
-Same.
Me too.
Whatever.
Let's make a fire.
Yeah.
Alice, didn't you have
that lighter in your--
No, it's alright.
I can take it out, it's alright.
Don't worry about that, ahem.
That's alright.
There you go.
It's alright.
Thanks.
Maybe we could sleep
back-to-back.
Keep our bodies
off the wet ground.
I'm just struggling
with why we're listening to her.
It's not like she's got
a great scorecard
in life-and-death situations.
Shut the fuck up.
You can lean up against me.
No, I'm good.
What, you the first college kid
that don't drink?
Live a little.
Suit yourself.
I'm telling you now,
if I get in a sticky situation,
I'm definitely throwing her
out front as gator chow.
You're so bad.
You have no idea.
Yes, please.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Damian...
Oh, fuck.
Damian!
Don't you dare hang up!
Hello? Hello, Damian?
It's Rufus. Can you hear me?
Oh, sweet Jesus.
This doesn't make any sense.
Why the hell
are they attacking us?
You got any ideas?
Look, my friend, if you know
something, now is the time.
-Come on, Frank!
-Hey, give him a second.
-Frank?
-There's been rumours.
Gators acting strange.
Strange like how?
Captain Sully, hello?
Quick.
Fast.
Normally, gators disappear
on the sight or sound of people,
but these, they're frenzied,
covering serious distance.
Aggressive.
Strange attack habits.
Out to kill.
Not just to eat.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
Ain't that just fucking sweet.
The locals have even named one.
Christina.
-The scarred one.
-Guys, look.
It's a cabin or something.
Hey, I think that'll give us
a vantage point.
At least we can see
what's coming.
Figure out our next move.
It's here!
Hey, stop.
Guys, don't move.
What do you see?
There.
Oh, shit.
And there.
Fuck.
Kyle.
Not everyone is gonna make it.
Stay there, OK?
Stay there.
OK, guys, listen up.
We're gonna run together, OK?
Tight. As a group.
We'll be bigger and more
threatening as a unit.
Remember...
gators never attack
anything bigger than them.
Wait! Wait!
Malika!
Kyle!
-Zoe!
I got you. I got you.
Guys! Together!
Malika!
Bitch!
Move!
Close the door!
Get it in! Get it in!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Fuck.
Help me!
Help me, please!
Shit.
OK, sorry, sorry.
You're gonna breathe, OK?
What the hell is that?
What are they doing?
They're killing each other?
We need to get some sleep.
I think we should take turns
taking watch.
Yeah.
Give me the money!
I'll kill the kid.
- I have to do something.
- No!
Jamie, please, no.
No, Jamie, don't leave me.
- I'm serious!
- Please!
I'll kill the kid!
Three, two...
Jamie.
Kyle.
Kyle!
I think I got something.
Where'd you get this?
Stuffed in a drawer.
If this X is us
and this is where we crashed,
and this is where we just came
through, right?
Is that a building?
And a building of that size
could be a factory or something.
If we cross
this small river here,
then a three-mile trek,
we can get to where
we gotta get to.
Hopefully, there's somebody
there to help us.
Yeah, or at least maybe
a radio or something.
I've never seen that building
on any map before.
That could be bullshit.
It could be someone doodling.
Are you sure?
Uh, my geography
is pretty rusty, but...
Yeah.
OK.
Kyle?
I am really sorry
that I wasn't there for you.
Guys, what the hell?
Are we just gonna
ignore the fact
this is four miles
in the wrong direction?
Not to mention the thing
that we're running from.
-Any better ideas, Sherlock?
-Yeah, we stay here.
The cabin is safer,
but we have no food,
no one is coming to get us,
and Zoe's condition
is getting worse.
So it's either stay here
and die, or try to survive.
I'm not doing this anymore.
I'm not pretending
like this is all OK.
Do you guys even know
why we're here?
- Malika--
- Do you?
We're here to scatter
our friend,
your brother's, ashes.
Why? Because she let him die.
Now we're all putting our lives
in her hands to do the same.
Even her best friend blames her.
That's enough.
Let's face it, we all liked
Jamie more than her.
It's not fair
that she got to live!
-That's enough!
-You shouldn't have his ashes!
-Hey!
-Hey, cool the fuck out!
Whatever the fuck happened
to you people in the past
has no place here.
None of that matters right now.
What matters is getting the fuck
out of here.
Fuck you all.
We're outgunned. Outnumbered.
To have even a small chance,
we gotta stick together.
Now we'll take a vote.
All those in favour
of staying here,
raise your hand.
All those that want to risk it
out there?
That's settled.
Now, Kyle...
can you tell us
how to get by these things?
You can do this.
If you face off
with one of them,
if they stare you in the eye,
don't try and hold your ground.
Just turn around and run
and don't look back.
Don't even run in a zigzag
because those gators
can get up to 24 miles an hour
if you let them.
However, they do burn out
pretty quick.
Then if they get you,
don't try wasting your energy
by freeing your body,
even if it's your head,
because those jaws
host 80 teeth.
They can rip through your skull,
through sheet metal,
through your bones.
The only way
that you can get free
is if you punch them
in the snout.
You gouge their eyes out.
And you got to do all of that
before they hit water
and pull you under.
Because when they do,
they're gonna spin you around
faster than a propeller.
They're gonna rip your body
into tiny little pieces.
And then they're gonna shove you
under a rock
and save your body for later.
Come on, come on, come on.
- I can't go on.
- What?
Oh, I can't go on.
-I can't.
-Hey.
Hey, I love you.
I'm not leaving without you.
Our little girl's back home
wondering where you are.
If she wants to stay,
maybe we should just let her.
Either way, we should not
be standing still right now.
-What the fuck?
-What did you say?
You are some piece of work.
-What?
-I...
-What do you want to do?
-I really want her to die.
Is that-- Is that bad?
No.
I think there's a queue
that goes round the block.
Come on.
Not giving her the satisfaction.
I really need
a fucking cheeseburger.
Andale.
Wait.
Y'all hear that?
It's the river.
Let's go.
Come on, come on. Let's go.
Do you need help?
-Do you need help?
-I got you.
Some geography, man.
We're screwed.
No.
No, no, no, that was the rain.
Good idea, they said.
Cross the stream
and stroll to safety, they said.
We should've stayed put.
We gotta go back.
No, we can't go back now.
What are we supposed to do?
We can't cross it.
Yeah, but we could use it
to our advantage.
Stream's gonna get wider
the further it goes down,
which means we can't cross it.
But the current flows
in the direction of the sea,
which is south-east.
Which is the direction
of the building.
Guys, it's running right by it.
What good does that do?
She wants to build a raft.
-She's check out.
-A raft?
Are you fucking kidding me?
- A raft?
- It's not crazy.
I've made one before.
There's logs everywhere.
Damp trees, which means bark
to lash them together.
Use our clothes
to make up the rest.
It has to hold eight people.
Yeah, but it doesn't need
to last that long.
With the current, it'll take us
a quarter of the time.
Aren't you forgetting the one
thing that we're running from?
We can't just stand here
and do arts and crafts.
After last night's rainfall,
it's seriously humid out.
And the gators can't regulate
their body temperature,
which means they're laying low
somewhere, cooling down.
That gives us enough time
until the sun starts to drop.
Pray tell, what happens if we
don't finish in a few hours?
They're gonna resurface
in numbers.
And we're cornered when they do.
Meaning we get ripped to shreds
and eaten.
-Is that about right?
-Not if we move quickly.
Not if we stick together.
- It's suicide.
- Come on, guys.
Let's get to work.
Do you want me to stay with her?
Please.
Careful, OK?
Sure.
OK. Put it down.
Good work, guys.
Alright!
So, we just need probably...
ten more like that.
Let's go, Frank. Let's go, Sam.
Is she for real?
One...
Alright.
We got it.
Hey.
We're nearly there.
I'm gonna get you home, baby.
I promise.
OK.
Baby, I know.
Guys.
Oh, shit.
- You good?
- Yeah, I'm good.
It's all that cadet training,
huh?
Where's Alice?
She's right behind us.
Or at least she was.
Shit!
I see you, fucker.
We have to go back.
Come on.
No, I am not leaving
without her.
Kyle, we have to go now.
Come on.
I'm here.
Oh, my God. You're bleeding.
-Alice...
-It's not mine. We have to go.
- They're coming.
- You good?
Quickly. Let's go. Let's move!
Come on. Hurry.
Alright.
The bag! Jamie's ashes.
Go, go! I've got it! Go!
- Sam!
- Go! Shit, hurry up!
Fuck! Go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Run! Sam, throw it!
You got it! Come on!
Let's go.
-Come on!
-Let's get the fuck outta here!
Go! Go!
They're getting closer!
I know!
Move!
-Push!
-Shit.
- Frank!
- We're going.
- Push!
- Come on, Frank!
Come on, Frank!
They're gaining on us, Frank!
Go!
Help push!
Come on!
They're getting closer!
- Frank!
- Come on, Frank.
Frank? Frank!
Quit backing out!
- Move!
- I'm moving!
I love you.
Frank, give me the stick!
Frank!
Zoe?
Shit!
Frank! Hey!
Zoe, come with me!
Zoe!
Zoe?
Zoe! Zoe!
No!
Please!
Hey, you can do this.
We're nearly there, OK?
It's just about one foot
in front of the other now.
I promised I'd get her home.
Don't make this all
be for nothing.
What do you think happened?
These are
armour-piercing rounds.
The type special Feds use.
Feds? Like police?
Feds like DEA armed units.
Plus, this place
not being on the map,
I'm guessing a drugs bust.
No.
I didn't come all this way
to get shot in the fucking head.
Well, whatever happened here
is long finished.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I believe we just decided
we're going in.
Well, be quiet about it.
We don't know
who could still be in there.
Ugh!
Hello!
See? No one home.
She's not worth it.
- What the fuck?
- Oh, my God.
What the fuck
happened here, man?
Guys?
Oh, my God.
Guys, look.
What is this?
We should split up.
I agree.
We'll cover more ground
that way.
They're running in two
directions, so two teams.
I'll go with Alice and Malika.
We follow the lines.
Find a phone, radio.
Make a call for help,
meet outside.
We good?
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
Um...
For God's sake,
keep quiet about it.
Let's go.
Hey, it's OK.
Aah!
Fuck.
I think this is the way.
We should eliminate the other
as an option.
Alice, you want to check it out?
Yeah, sure. I'll catch up.
What the hell is this?
This must be
what's making them go crazy.
It's their unmatched ferocity.
Kyle! Whoa!
Oh, my God.
Why are you looking at me
like that?
I see you.
What type of pop ballad
shit is that?
Digging at Maude.
Chipping at Kyle.
Leaving Zoe for dead. Twice.
Looking after number one.
You think I didn't see that shit
in the cabin?
God, relax.
You're being intense.
I know people like you!
Seen them in the war.
Stepping on everyone else.
Throw someone off a cliff
if it saved your own skin.
No code.
-Hey, are you OK?
-They're everywhere.
- Can't go out.
- Who?
Hey. Hello?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Stay with us, stay with us.
Frank!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
How does it feel?
Like shit! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Hey! Hey!
Oh, fuck.
He's gone.
Shit.
-Kyle.
-Hey.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, he's fucking dead.
Where's Frank and Malika?
God, I'm begging you,
please!
Please! I'm serious!
Please! I'm sorry!
What the fuck am I doing?
Help!
Please!
I got you, I got you!
Come on, guys.
It's OK.
Shh, alright.
Where's Frank?
I think that thing got him.
It's OK, Malika.
You're safe.
You're safe now.
I'm sorry.
I just miss him.
Me too.
Let's go home.
We need to go there.
I can see it.
- I can see...
- No, no, no, no.
-Come.
-No.
They're sleeping.
Be as quiet as possible.
Go slow.
OK.
Come on, Sam.
Hello.
Come on!
Hey!
No!
No! Sam!
Hello, do you read me?
Yes! Yes! Hello!
We crashed! We were--
We were in an airplane!
I don't know, we crashed
in the middle of a field!
-Can you give me your position?
-I don't know! Fuck!
We're in a building!
We're in the swamps
by the river!
Building complex by the swamps.
Hold tight and I'll get to you.
Hello?!
-What the fuck is happening?
-Power's down.
Dom, don't.
Stay here and die.
Or try to survive.
Yeah.
OK. Let's go.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
- Alice...
- Alice.
What the fuck is that?
This is what you want, right?
- Alice?
- I'm alright.
This is yours.
No!
Kyle!
-Shoot!
-Go, go, go!
-Alice!
Dom!
Move!
Fuck!
Come on, you motherfucker!
Hey, Christina.
Fuck you!
OK, big bro.
It's time.
I'm living life now, dude.
Thank you.
Hiding away,
thinking about preserving life,
just means
you're not living it.
I need a drink.
Um...
You hold on to it.
When we get back out here,
you're going on this thing.